<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mind the Grow</title>
    <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mind the Grow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.mindthegrow.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/analytics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/agriculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/agriculture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Assurance in Extraction and Potency Testing</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/chemistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/chemistry/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Consulting</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/services/investment/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/location/</guid>
      <description>REQUIREMENTS  No residential zones.
 Must be at least 1000ft from schools, child care locations, city-owned recreational centers, or drug/alcohol treatment facilities.
 CCEs must be established in an area which will give community support to the existence and operation of the enterprise (see below).
 Proof of possession of the premises where the CCE is located with a valid zone-use permit and most recent certificate of occupancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Consumption License</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/work/socialconsumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/work/socialconsumption/</guid>
      <description>Proposition A client approached us with interest in exploring the feasibility of opening up a new Cannabis Consumption Enterprise in Denver, CO (our home-base!).
The passing of Initiative 300 to legalize designated areas for the consumption of cannabis products was exciting, but the legal hoops to jump through are numerous, so it is no surprise that there is a severe paucity of operational businesses. At the time of this writing (mid-2018), only two are operational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/community/</guid>
      <description>REQUIREMENTS  For any suitable location, take note of all registered neighborhood organizations (RNO) in the district.
 You should receive written approval/endorsement from at least one such eligible organization.
 Craft formal plan to create positive impacts in the neighborhood where the licensed premises are located.
  The full outline of what constitutes licensing requirements can be found in Sec. 6-210 of the DRMC.
CHALLENGES  Find the organizations with which you will engage to craft a plan for community engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administration</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/admin/</guid>
      <description>REQUIREMENTS  Description of proposed hours of operation. You should review the Lawful Presence Affidavit for more information.
 A &amp;ldquo;Responsible Operations Plan,&amp;rdquo; which details how &amp;ldquo;employees will monitor and prevent over-intoxication, underage access to the DCA, driving under the influence of marijuana, the illegal distribution of marijuana or marijuna products within DCA, and any other potential criminal activity on the premises.&amp;rdquo;
 A documented employee training program that addresses all components of the Responsible Operations Plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/cce/design/</guid>
      <description>REQUIREMENTS  A health and sanitation plan for sanitization and cleaning of cannabis consumption accessories to be rented or otherwise made available for use. Information on Health Inspections can be found on Denver&amp;rsquo;s government website.
 A marijuana waste plan that includes a detailed description of how employees will dispose of any Waste that is left, abandoned, or otherwise not consumed on the premises.
 An odor control and abatement plan in the same form and substance as would be required in DRMC Sec 4-10, and any rules promulgated thereto, if the applicant intends to allow smoking or vaping of marijuana within the Designated Consumption Area (DCA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/blogs/</guid>
      <description>The Green Rush has resulted in a skewed marketplace subject to price volatility. Diversification is the key to weathering the storm of wild market swings. Identifying strategies to find a sustainable market niche is becoming a necessity. No matter how uncertain or complex your problem seems, Mind the Grow provides you with custom solutions for all stages of the agricultural production cycle, from seed to store
Insights We dig deep into your company’s data to discover opportunities and problem areas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>