<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Investment and Entrepreneurship on Mind the Grow</title>
    <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Investment and Entrepreneurship on Mind the Grow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannabis Consumption Enterprises</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/cce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/cce/</guid>
      <description>Problem The Social Consumption License created by [Initiative 300][1] in Denver, CO is so new that very little information exists online. A client approached us to perform a preliminary investigation into what is required to get started.
Approach We compiled a report that categorized the main obstacles and linked to resources for accomplishing the requirements. The focus was on clarity of exposition and brevity.
Outcome The client decided the location requirements were prohibitively expensive and chose not to pursue the project further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Growth Hacking</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/growth/</guid>
      <description>Problem Growth is central to survival. Understanding where inefficiencies lie in your business can help catapult you to the next level.
Approach We aim to provide you with clear and concise information to address your most pressing questions and concerns.
Outcome We identify problems and find new sectors for expansion. By using cutting-edge mathematical and computer-science tools, we simulate potential revenue streams to gain deeper insights into your plans for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investment Consulting</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/opportunity/investment/</guid>
      <description>Problem Funders want to know the risks of their ventures, and we bridge the gap between their concerns and your ambitions.
Approach We help you actualize goals into reality by crafting rigorous business plans. As you already know, big plans come with big unknowns. Let us quantify them.
By helping you identify and assess risks, we allow your business to try new ideas without sacrificing potential profits.
Outcome We turn idealistic goals into realistic implementation strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>