<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Solutions on Mind the Grow</title>
    <link>/solutions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Solutions on Mind the Grow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepeneurship &amp; Investment</title>
      <link>/solutions/growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/growth/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CadoCast</title>
      <link>/solutions/cadocast/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/cadocast/</guid>
      <description>Avocados Today Avocados are trending. Sales have grown tremendously over the past decade due to factors such as cuisine trends (avocado toast) and diet crazes (Paleo and KETO diets). But it is not merely fads that drive sales. The Avocado is a vital staple of the North American diet. Thousands of fast-casual restaurants and Tuesday night taco dinners rely on the creamy fruit to supply flavor and nutrients. The forecast clearly demonstrates that sales will only grow higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rigorous Insights through Data-Driven Agriculture</title>
      <link>/solutions/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/analytics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoffeeCode</title>
      <link>/solutions/coffeecode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/coffeecode/</guid>
      <description>Coffee Today Coffee is the third most popular beverage in the world, following water and tea. It is especially prevalent in American culture, with an estimated 450 million cups consumed daily (in the United States alone). It is primarily consumed for its stimulating properties, but it is also a cultural habit in all walks of life.
In recent years, coffee culture has blown to astronomical proportions. Coffee is no longer just a drink for the break room, but it is an entire experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MateMapper</title>
      <link>/solutions/matemapper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/matemapper/</guid>
      <description>Yerba Mate Yerba Mate (or Hierba Mate) is a caffeinated tea native to South America that has been used for centuries as a stimulant and health supplement. It was originally used by the indigenous Guaraní people of South America, but its use became common practice since the colonization of the Americas.
In the past years, Mate has become a popular beverage around the world. Although it’s traditionally consumed with a filter-straw (bombilla) from a small cup called a gourd, the “mainstreamization” of the tea has created an immense market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannalytics</title>
      <link>/solutions/cannalytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/cannalytics/</guid>
      <description>Note:
Move descriptions into text, make non-summary, product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Assurance, Extraction, and Testing</title>
      <link>/solutions/chemistry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/chemistry/</guid>
      <description>Precision Testing equipment has some natural variation built in to it that scientists are used to handling. However, classical statistical methods fail to address the natural variability present in different batches of product.
The approach we take is rooted in cutting-edge computational mathematics to maximize the utility of information and address the underlying uncertainty in potency inherent to the cannabis plants.
Efficiency We can use the latest developments from simulation-based optimal experimental design to adapt your testing regiments to budgetary and temporal constraints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability</title>
      <link>/solutions/sustainability/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/solutions/sustainability/</guid>
      <description>Responsible Agriculture Less water. Less fertilizer. Less waste. Fewer pesticides. We are all collective stewards of our environment. These goals may seem at odds with profit margins, but through creative solutions and robust analytics, we help you achieve responsible growth for your plants and your business.
Sustainability It is a principle ingrained in to everything we do. It cannot just be a buzzword.
Sustainability practices are vital for maintaining steady product yields and a healthy environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>