<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Opportunity on Mind the Grow</title>
    <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/categories/opportunity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Opportunity on Mind the Grow</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.mindthegrow.com/categories/opportunity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Support for Startups</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/startups/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Development</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/bizdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/bizdev/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/markets/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Market Research</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/markets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/markets/</guid>
      <description>Problem Business owners are too busy managing day-to-day operations to devote any significant amount of time to researching. Decisions about the potential size of markets for new products are difficult to make without an understanding of the influence of estimation. Uncertainties at each step of the research process can compound and lead to conclusions about the potential revenue to be wildly inaccurate.
Approach We identify the quantities of interest relevant to your specific problem and then hone in on what data to collect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Development</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/bizdev/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/bizdev/</guid>
      <description>Problem Growth is central to survival. Understanding where inefficiencies lie in your business can help catapult you to the next level.
Approach We aim to provide you with clear and concise information to address your most pressing questions and concerns.
Outcome We identify problems and find new sectors for expansion. By using cutting-edge mathematical and computer-science tools, we simulate potential revenue streams to gain deeper insights into your plans for growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support for Startups</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/startups/</guid>
      <description>Problem Funders want to know the risks of their ventures, and we bridge the gap between their concerns and your ambitions.
Approach We help you actualize goals into reality by crafting rigorous business plans. As you already know, big plans come with big unknowns. Let us quantify them.
By helping you identify and assess risks, we allow your business to try new ideas without sacrificing potential profits.
Outcome We turn idealistic goals into realistic implementation strategies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Consumption License</title>
      <link>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/socialconsumption/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mindthegrow.com/casestudies/socialconsumption/</guid>
      <description>Problem A client approached us with interest in exploring the feasibility of opening up a new Cannabis Consumption Enterprise in Denver, CO (our home-base!).
The passing of Initiative 300 to legalize designated areas for the consumption of cannabis products was exciting, but the legal hoops to jump through are numerous, so it is no surprise that there is a severe paucity of operational businesses. At the time of this writing (mid-2018), only two are operational.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>